And you'll find that out. You'll be finding it out very soon.
You should see what we have on these people.
These are bad people. These are people
that want to destroy our country.
We're not going to let it happen.
They've used armed gangs to assault local police
in cities nationwide,
and they have attacked journalists
reporting on their crimes.
So the journalists that report on their crimes,
don't worry, you're very safe.
I hope that's not going to turn you around.
But they have been very threatening to people.
But we're going to be very threatening to them,
far more threatening to them than they ever were with us.
And that includes the people that fund them.
Probably some of the people I know,
some of the people I dine with.
But if they do, they're in deep trouble.
So we're going to be looking very strongly
at the people that are funding these operations.
When you see the signs, and they're all made out of
a beautiful, beautiful paper, beautiful, nice, stiff,
very expensive paper with beautiful wood handles,
all the same, all the same color.
They come from very expensive printing machines.
These are not people that write out their signs.
These are not people that live in a basement,
that believe in something.
These are paid anarchists.
At least three of these courageous journalists
have personally been victims of Antifa attacks.
Andy Ngo has been repeatedly beaten by Antifa thugs
for his work in cruel, Andy is.